

Las Cruces, NM

Linked in

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

As an accomplished technical support and sales professional, I've spent over 15 years building relationships, honing my analytical thinking, and perfecting my empathic listening and strategic questioning skills. But I knew that there was more I could do to revolutionize the industry. With a love for math and a passion to solve complex problems, I have set out to create intelligent systems that could overcome any challenge. Alongside a team of equally passionate and ambitious individuals, we will tackle non-obvious problems and overcome obstacles that others deemed impossible.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Teleperformance, Remote

Team Manager AppleCare Tier 3

4/2018 - 12/2022

- Motivated team to consistently exceed production target by 32% by establishing crucial problem-solving protocols.
- Achieved and retained the highest screen share rate and a 95% cx satisfaction rating out of 300 plus employees.
- Solved issues with extensive product knowledge of all; hardware, OS, software, services, accessories, and peripherals.
- Actively listened to determine the best timing to showcase upsells.

#### Encantada, Las Cruces, NM

Sales Manager / Public Liaison

11/2015 - 3/2018

- Closed 60+ real-estate deals achieving 84% inbound capacity while acting as the community liaison.
- Utilized CRM to coordinate multiple accounts maintaining consistent communication among clients.
- Reinforced manager's preferences for working with business on multiple projects increasing efficiency by 24%.
- Exceeded 6% of quota with a successful multiple-location promotional campaign creating 18 referrals.

### Zozude, Las Cruces, NM

Director of Outreach

6/2013 - 10/2015

- Increased annual conference attendance objective by 66%.
- Developed an email marketing campaign that expanded membership by 73%.
- Cold-called potential leads and scheduled remote meetings to present products to teams.
- Improved referral stats by emphasizing consistent empathetic communication establishing rapport and questioning essential to product development.

## **CORE TRAITS**

- Relationship Building
- Character
- Sales

### TOOLS

- Hubspot "Certified"
- Mail Chimp
- Grammarly
- Scribe
- macOS, iOS, iWork
- Workspace, Android
- MS 365, Office, Exel
- Zoom, Zapier, ChatGPT

### **PROJECTS**

- Applecare Production Enhancement Team
- Encantada Community Betterment Project
- Zozude Product Development Team
- NMSU Transportation Growth Project
- WSNM Boardwalk Removal
- Special Olympics Swim Coach
- Oñate Website Designer

# EDUCATION

- New Mexico State Univ
- Bachelor of Science
  Mechanical Engineering
- Minor Math

## **EXTRACURRICULAR**

- Baja SAE
- ASCE Concrete Canoe
- ASME AG-1
- ASNMSU Homecoming Chair
- International Soccer Captain